<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<description>        
    <text key="jms-serverType.storage"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures storage information for persistent message.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.fixed-client-id"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="durable-subscriberType.destination-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is destination name in which Durable Subscriber receives message.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.thread-pool"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of establishing connection from this connection by Factory client,
                        thread pool information on this connection is set.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="service-config.use-ssl"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This configures whether to apply SSL to server channel.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jms-thread-poolType.max"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures maximum size of thread pool.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jms-serverType.queue-cluster"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element selects Queue clustering method.
                    ]]>        
    </text>        
            
    <text key="storageType.file-storage"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures file storage in case of using file storage.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="db-storageType.message-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures message table name used in JMS.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="service-config.client-limit"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This configures maximum number of client in which server channel allows.
                        In case of using blocking socket,it can not exceed the maximum number of threads set in message broker.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="destinationType.broker-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify name of the broker routing the incoming message to this destination.
                         Unless specified, the message will be routed to the destination of the server that connected to connection factory.
                         If specified, even though the destination is connected to another clustering server, the messages sent by the procedure in this destination 
                         will be routed to the specified broker, but not to the destination of connected server.
                         Please do not use this option for clustering destination. 
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.embedded"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Option to use embedded DB as storage.
                        
                    ]]>        
    </text>
              
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.ip-address"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is ip-address of related JMS message broker.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-serverType.service-config"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:This is configuration on service channel for providing messaging service. Minimum one should be configured.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="destinationType.low-mark"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures memory size starting soft caching.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-storageType.transaction-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures XA table name used in JMS.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="service-config.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This is name of service channel. This is used for configuring channel information in Connection Factory.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-tcp-address.port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is service port number of related server channel.
                        [Example]: 9741
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-thread-poolType.min"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures minimum size of thread pool.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-thread-poolType.keep-alive-time"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: For thread which has not been used for set time period and exceeds min number, thread will be destroyed.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-serverType.topic-cluster"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element selects topic clustering method.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
                
    <text key="service-config.client-keepalive-timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: When the connection with client has been abruptly terminated,  this is the time period in which it will wait for reconnection.
                        After time period has been passed, it will return the resource to the server.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.broker-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This is name used for communicating between clusters.
                        JMS message broker taking part in clustering should contain unique value.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-server"><![CDATA[
                [Description]:  The top level element inside JMSMain.xml.
                Token or String values can not include following strings. ':', ',', '*', '?', '='
            ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-storageType.destination-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures destination table name used in JMS.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="service-config.backlog-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Backlog size of service port.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="jms-serverType.connection-factory"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures information on connection factory.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
                 
    <text key="service-config.read-buffer-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: The size of network buffer reading message from client. The default value is 64K.
                    ]]>                
    </text>
         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.broker-selection-policy"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Determine the policy to select the channel when ConnectionFactory creates connection.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
                 
    <text key="connection-factoryType.client-id"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is ClientID value being set as default value in generated conection using related Connection Factory.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-serverType.jms-server-cluster"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures JMS message broker participating in here in case of using destination clustering.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="service-config.write-buffer-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Size of network buffer for transmitting message to Client. The default value is 64K.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="topic-clusterType.topic-cluster-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configure clustering type for clustering topic.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-server-clusterType.cluster-service"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures service name for communcation between clusterings. If it is not set,
		                it is temporarily configured.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="file-storageType.path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This is full file path in which file storage is located.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.weight"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This value is used in case of using message distribution mode of server-weighted mode.  
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-serverType.thread-pool"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:This element is configuration on thread pool in which JMS message broker uses.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="db-storageType.durable-message-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures subscription table name used in JMS.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="service-config.connection-timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:In case of using blocking socket, it terminates the connection  when there is no request from client for the set time.
                         The default value is 120 minutes.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="queue-clusterType.local-preference"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: It enhances the importnace of message processed in local broker.
                        This is only meaningful in case where either of server-weighted or consumer-weighted mode is used.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="durable-subscriberType.client-id"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This tag configures value determining client.
                        Entire client-id values within durable-subscriber element should not be duplicated
                        not only in connection-factory element but also in durable-subscirber element.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.jms-port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is service prot value of JMS message broker.
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
                     
    <text key="jms-tcp-address.server-address"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: IP address of related server channel is directly configured. This is used as address value for connecting to client.
                                If it is not set, "127.0.0.1" will be used.
                        [Example]: 123.123.123.123
                    ]]>                    
    </text>
         
    <text key="service-config.ssl-configuration"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:  Specify the variables for SSL.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
                     
    <text key="connection-factoryType.type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configuring information on connection factory.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.clustered-factory"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the range of connection factory. If it is set as true, it will be used as cluster factory.
            		]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is the name of Connection Factory used for management purpose in JMS System.
		            ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="connection-factoryType.export-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Name in which Connection Factory is binded in naming server.
		                If it has not been set, name property will be used as it is.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="destinationType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is the destination name used for management purpose within JMS message broker.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="service-config.blocking-socket"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:  It determines whether to use blocking socket or non-blocking-socket for JMS server
                         It is recommended to use non-blocking socket.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
                        
    <text key="durable-subscriberType.message-selector"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures message selector of Durable Subscriber.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="storageType.db-storage"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures database storage in case of using database storage.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="db-storageType.data-source-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: This element configures name of datasource to be binded in JNDI to be used.
                 ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="jms-serverType.access-log"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:This element configures inforamtion on access log.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="jms-serverType.durable-subscriber"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures information on Durable subscriber.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.broker-id"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is broker id used for communication among clusters.
		                JMS Message broker taking part in cluster should contain each unique value.
                        If the value has not been set, it can be temporaily configured according to set order in cluster table.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="jms-serverType.broker-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:This element is name of JMS message broker. If it is not set, host name is used.
                    ]]>                        
    </text>
         
    <text key="destinationType.consumer-limit"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Limit the number of consumers for accessing to destination.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
                         
    <text key="destinationType.local-distribute"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: It determines whether to do message distribution of queue destination set as multiple-receiver.
                        One of round-robin or random can be configured.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="destinationType.high-mark"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures memory size starting to use flow control.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="connection-factoryType.service"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures name of service attempting to be connected by Connection Factory.
                            Name set in service-config is used.
                            In case where name is not set, it is configured as initially set service.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="topic-clusterType.relay-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This is method of delivering message to cluster server set above. Either of non-durable or durable can be configured.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="destinationType.type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures type of related destination. Select either of queue or topic.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="queue-clusterType.queue-cluster-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configure clustering type for queue clustering.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="jms-server-clusterType.jms-server-info"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures information on JMS message broker taking part in Cluster.
                    ]]>                            
    </text>
                             
    <text key="destinationType.topic-cluster-name"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Select set clustering type as topic-cluster.
                        ]]>                            
    </text>
         
                             
    <text key="topic-clusterType.target"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures broker name participating in clustering. Related name should be name set in jms-server-info.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="destinationType.export-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Name for related destination to be binded into naming server. If it is not set, name property is used as it is.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="jms-serverType.destination"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures information on destination.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="destinationType.limit"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures maximum memory size can be used in related destination.
                        In case where used memory exceeds this value, message delivering of client will process as an error.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="queue-clusterType.target"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures broker name participating in clustering. Related name should be name set in jms-server-info.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="queue-clusterType.cluster-distribute"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configure method for distributing message in each broker participating in queue clustering.
                        One of server-weighted, consumer-weighted, round-robin or random can be set.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="destinationType.queue-cluster-name"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Select clustering type set as queue-cluster.
                        ]]>                                
    </text>
                                 
    <text key="durable-subscriberType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element is the name of Durable Subscriber used for management purpose within message broker.
                    ]]>                                
    </text>
     
    <text key="destinationType.multiple-receiver"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify whether to allow multiple receivers for the distributed processing of queue type destination.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
    
       <text key="service-config.check-security"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies whether authority checks are to be performed for client activities.
                        If set to true, only users that have createConnection authority for jeus.jms.client.connectionFactory will be able to 
                        connect to this service channel. Also only users that have createDestination authority for jeus.jms.destination.creation                     
                        will be able to to dynamically add destinations to JMS message broker while it is running. 
                 
                  ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="service-config.server-url"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies the URL for the service channel. Set this item to 'oneport' for a 1-port service channel, and set to 'tcp://host:port' for a 'tcp' channels.
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="destinationType.max-pending-limit"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:If MessageListener is registered in Queue or Topic, incoming messages will be sent to Consumer as soon as they arrive at
                        Destination. Thus the client will have to handle these messages quickly or they will accumulate in memory and an OutOfMemory error will occur.
                        This problem can be prevented by specifying the maximum allowable number of messages to be dispatched to applications without receiving an ACK message.
                      
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="destinationType.resume-dispatch-factor"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: If the number of messages in the PENDING queue is higher than specified in max-pending-limit, message transmissions will temporarily be suspended.
                                       If the number of messages in the PENDING queue drops to the the number specified in (max-pending-limit * resume-dispatch-factor)or less,
                                       after the client had completed message processing and had sent an ACKNOWLGE,  
                                       message transmission will resume.
                                      
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="storageType.reliability-level"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies the level of reliability for storing messages.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="storageType.delete-invalid-destinations"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies whether the destination, recovered from storage but not specified in JMSMain.xml, is to be removed when the engine is started. 
                                          ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="embeddedType.path"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Specifies the path for embedded DB storage.
                        ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.destination-table-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing destination information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.durable-subscriber-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing durable subscriber information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.message-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing message information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.user-property-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing user information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.durable-message-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing durable message information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.xa-table-name"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the name of the table for storing XA information.
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.sql-poll-timeout"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies the wait time for SQLCommandExecutor, which implements database tasks in the background, to retrieve SQL commands from the SQL Queue. 

                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="db-storageType.wait-sql-executor"><![CDATA[
					    [Description]: Specifies whether to wait for the jobs in the SQL Queue to finish before terminating SQLCommandExecutor.
					                        ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="jms-server-infoType.oneport"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This option should be set to true if JMS Service Channel provides services to OnePort Transport.
                        ip-address and jms-port should be the base ports of JEUSManager or the EngineContainer.
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="jms-server-infoType.ssl-configuration"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:  Specifies the configuration of SSL. 
                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="jms-server-infoType.connection-interval"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:Sets the interval for connecting with other cluster servers.
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="reliability-levelType.produce"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Sends messages in storage but does not log inforamtion when the messages are sent to consumers. 
                            If an ACKNOWLEDGE that a consumer has sent could not be handled due to storage failure, it will be marked as unstransmitted and can be resent when the failure is corrected.

                    ]]>     
    </text>
     
    <text key="reliability-levelType.consume"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Sends messages in storage and logs inforamtion when the messages are sent to consumers. 
                             If an ACKNOWLEDGE that a consumer has sent could not be handled due to storage failure, it will be marked as transmitted and will be stored in the pending queue of the destination.
                             Messages in the pending queue can be deleted or retransmitted by an administrator. 
                       
                    ]]>     
    </text>
                                 
    <ref key="service-config">jms-tcp-address</ref>
                       
</description>
