<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<description>        
    <text key="file-publishType.publish-path"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a directory where WSDL file is stored.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="http-publishType.wsdl-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a alternative URL to publish WSDL of 
                                Web service in addition to default published URL.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="securityType.response-sender"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element sets the security related configuration such as encryption and electronic signature to a SOAP response message to a Web Services client.
                                                        
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serviceType.wsdl-publish"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a WSDL publishing method.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="http-publishType.server-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a URL of a server that publishes the WSDL file of a deployed Web Services.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.port-component-name"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a name of a Web Services endpoint.
                            				This &lt;port-component-name> corresponds to &lt;port-component-name> found in webservice.xml.
                            [Dependency]:/webservices/webservice-description/port-component/port-component-name 
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="file-publishType.secure-server-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a SSL enabled URL of a server that publishes the WSDL file of a deployed Web Services.  
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.ejb-transport-guarantee"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element sets the confidentiality and integrity type of the messages communicated in EJB end-point.
                            Three types are available: 'NONE', 'CONFIDENTIAL' and 'INTEGRAL'. 
                            
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="wsdl-publishType.file-publish"><![CDATA[
                                [Description]: This element specifies a WSDL published in a file format.
                                Any schema imported from the published WSDL is referenced through a relative file path.
                                
                            ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="file-publishType.server-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a URL of a server that publishes the WSDL file of a deployed Web Services.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jeus-webservices-ddType.service-info-page"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This elements specifies which page deals with service info view requested by web browsers.
                                           The specified value is a relative URL of the page starting with "/".
                              
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ejb-login-configType.auth-method"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element sets an authentication method. Four methods are available: 'BASIC', 'CLIENT-CERT', 'DIGEST' and 'FORM'.  
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.transaction"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies use of WS-Transaction.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="securityType.request-receiver"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element sets the security related configuration such as encryption and electronic signature to a SOAP request messages from a Web Services client.
                                                         
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.rm"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies use of WS-ReliableMessaging.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.tie-class"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies the class that maps Web Services end-point URL with Web Services end-point interface.
                            It is automatically generated during deployment.
                           
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.soapver"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies the version of a SOAP message serviced by deployed Web Services. 
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.security"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element sets the security type of Web Services (WS-Security). 
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ejb-login-configType.realm-name"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element configures the domains where security policy is applied.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.ejb-endpoint-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a URL of an EJB endpoint. This is used only with EJB endpoint.
                            
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serviceType.webservice-description-name"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a name of a Web Services endpoint in the corresponding WSDL file.
                                           This &lt;webservice-description-name> corresponds to &lt;webservice-description-name> found in webservice.xml.  
                            [Dependency]:/webservices/webservice-description/webservice-description-name    
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="http-publishType.secure-server-url"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a SSL enabled URL of a server that publishes the WSDL file of a deployed Web Services.  
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jeus-webservices-ddType.ejb-context-path"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a Context path of an endpoint URL for EJB Web Services.
                            
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jeus-webservices-ddType.ejb-login-config"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies the client authentication method and domain for a EJB Web Services endpoint URL.
                           
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="portType.service-property"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: Specifies service endpoint property of each port.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jeus-webservices-dd"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element is a root element of JEUS Web Services deployment descriptor.
                ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serviceType.port"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies a port information of the Web Services.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="jeus-webservices-ddType.service"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies the deployed Web Services.  
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="wsdl-publishType.http-publish"><![CDATA[
                                [Description]: This element specifies a WSDL published in HTTP format.
                                Any schema imported from the published WSDL is referenced through HTTP URL.
                                
                            ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="rmType.client-provider"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element specifies that RM webservice runs in client mode. Default value is "false."
                        ]]>        
    </text>
 </description>
