<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<description>                  
    <text key="handlerPropertySetType.property"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Property to be delivered to handler is set.
                    ]]>                  
    </text>
                     
    <text key="rolePermissionType.principal"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Role related to user principal is set.
                        [Value Description]: Principal name set in accounts.xml of security.
                    ]]>                  
    </text>
                     
    <text key="schedulerType.job-list"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures job list to be registered in scheduler.
                    ]]>                  
    </text>
                     
    <text key="rolePermissionType.role"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Role name contributed to principals is set.
                    ]]>                  
    </text>
                     
    <text key="smtp-propertyGroup.from-address"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: The address of sender for email is set for this field. 
                    ]]>                  
    </text>
                     
    <text key="keystore-configType.truststore-path"><![CDATA[                        [Description]: Define truststore file path to be applied to current domain.                    ]]>                  
    </text>
            
    <text key="keystore-configType.keystore-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Defines keystore file path to be applied to current domain.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="propertyType.value"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: The value of property.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="file-handlerType.file-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: File name in which this handler uses will be set for this field.
										If user has not set for this field, default file name of each logger will be used.
										Please refer to JEUS Server Manual for each default file name.
                        [Example]: &lt;file-name>C:\logs\mylog.log&lt;/file-name>
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jndi-refType.jndi-info"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element binds as actual EJB JNDI name used in code.
				                        For example, it can lookup actual JNDI name "ACCEJB" (account EJB) as "ejb/account" within source code
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="job-listType.job"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures a single job to be registered in scheduler.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jsp-engineType.compile-option"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This is option used as Servlet compiler and is not commonly used.
                        [Value Description]: Compile option property used for compiling (Referencing &lt;java-compiler>element)
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="poolingType.period"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Time for object to be pooled is set for this field.
                        [Performance Recommendation]:As this value is bigger, time cycle will be enlarged and traffic on server operation will be decreased.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="run-as-identityType.principal-name"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Principal name used as role of run-as-specified-identity within ejb-jar.xml or web.xml.
                    [Value Description]: Principal name configured in subjects.xml of security.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="loggingGroup.handler"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: Handler to use in logger is set for this field.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jsp-engineType.jsp-work-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: JSP workdir is location in which Servlet source file and class files are stored.
						               Developer or administrator can use related directory for debugging purpose.
                                       This element is not generally needed to be used.
                        [Value Description]: Absolute path used for compliling JSP.
                        [Defined Value]: default : %SERVLET_HOME%\jspwork \enginename\GroupDocBase\DocBase
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="SecurityServicePropertyType.value"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Property value as selective matter.
                        [Value Description]: Property value.
                        [Example]: &lt;value>c:\security\myAccounts.xml&lt;/value>
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="rolePermissionType.classname"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Role permission class name to use is set. If it has not been set, it uses class in which JEUS provides as default.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="user-handlerType.formatter-class"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Fully qualified class name of formatter in which this handler is used.
										This class inherits java.util.logging.Formatter and jeus.util.logging.JeusFormatter will be constructed.
                        [Example]: &lt;formatter-class>com.tmax.logging.handler.MyHandler&lt;/formatter-class>
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="handlerType.user-handler"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: In case of using handler in which user has created according to J2SE logging API, this setting
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="common-handlerType.filter-class"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Fully qualified class name of filer class set in this handler is set for this field.
                    [Example]: &lt;filter-class>com.tmax.logging.filter.MyFilter&lt;/filter-class>
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="handlerType.file-handler"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: This is the handler to be used in case of displaying logging as file.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="user-handlerType.handler-property"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: When handler is generated, property to parse is set. These properties are delivered to
                                    handler as being stored in Map object as key-value through JeusHandler.setProperty() method.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jsp-engineType.compile-encoding"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This property is value of configuring in ?encoding option when compiling generated Servlet source file through parsing JSP files.
                                    This configuration is not commonly used. Web Container automatically selects proper configuration.
                    [Value Description]: Character set checking encoding scheme to use. For additional information, please refer to javac compiler documentation.
                    [Defined Value]: [default] : This is automatically selected in Web Container.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="SecurityServiceType.property"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element defines property as name-value pair in related security service as option.
                                    Please refer documentation on service class for explaination on each property which can be defined.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="rolePermissionType.unchecked"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This enables for users to use role without checking anything.
                    [Example]: &lt;unchecked/>
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="smtp-propertyGroup.smtp-host-address"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: The address of Smtp server to send email is set for this field.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jobType.name"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element configures job name.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jsp-engineType.check-included-jspfile"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: If this property is set as "true", it enables to recompile related JSP file when executing included JSP file.
                                   Included JSP files are not checked for being updated.
                    [Value Description]: Activating or inactivating this configuration as Boolean value.
                    [Value Type Description]: Boolean
                    [Defined Value]: [true] : Activating related configuration.
                                     [false]: Inactivating related configuration.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="handlerType.smtp-handler"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: This is the handler to use when sending logging to email.
                  [Performance Recommandation]: There is a warning when a huge amount of email exist without proper filter.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="smtp-propertyGroup.to-address"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: The address of receiver of email is set for this field.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="invoke-httpType.http-port"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element configures prot number of Web Server to process HTTP-RMI request.
                                    This Web Server/Web Container should be already in execution mode and RMI should be deployed.
                    [Value Description]: Port number of Web Server to be connected by HTTP-RMI stub.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="intervalType.millisecond"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Time cycel is configured in millisecond unit.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jobType.count"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: The number of execution for this job is configured.
                    [Defined Value]: [-1]: No limitation for number of execution.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="keystore-configType.truststore-password"><![CDATA[                        [Description]: Configure the password for truststore file to be applied to current domain..                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jobType.interval"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element configures time cycle for this job to executed.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="intervalType.minutely"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Time cycle is configured in minute unit.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="common-handlerType.encoding"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: Encoding in which this handler leaves message is set for this field.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="methodParamType.method-params"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Parameters of method are set by order.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="envType.value"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This value is used as parameter of corresponding wrapper class generator.
                    [Example]: &lt;value>100&lt;/value>
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="file-handlerType.buffer-size"><![CDATA[                        [Description]:Configure the size of buffer when this handler displays as file.                         [Value Description]: This is in the unit of byte.                        [Performance Recommandation]: As this value becomes larger, message 			to be displayed in file will be delayed, however, the performance of logging will be 			enhanced.                     ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="file-handlerType.valid-hour"><![CDATA[
                      [Description]: In case of using and updating frequently on the file in which this handler uses for a certain amount of time. This setting is used for updating time unit.
                                    In this case, used date and time will be automaticallly followed right after file name in which this handler uses.
                      [Value Description]: This represents in unit of hour and it should get divisor of 24 + N*24(n is integer greater than 0).
                      [Example]: &lt;valid-hour>3&lt;/valid-hour>
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="envType.type"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: JAVA type of environment variable.
                    [Value Description]: Select single Java Type among java.lang.Boolean, java.lang.String, java.lang.Integer, java.lang.Double, java.lang.Byte, java.lang.Short, java.lang.Long, java.lang.Float, java.lang.Character.
                    [Example]: &lt;type>java.lang.Integer&lt;/type>
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="handlerType.socket-handler"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: This element is handler used for sending to socket in which logging is set.
                  [Performance Recommandation]: The performance will be decreased without using proper filter since logging message is transmitted as one Socket.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="securityPermissionType.security-permission-spec"><![CDATA[
              [Description]: Security permission can be written and Java policy file is followed for the format.
              [Example]: grant {
                            permission java.lang.RuntimePermission "foo";
                        }
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="intervalType.hourly"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Time cycle is configured in time unit.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="poolingType.min"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: The mimimum value of being pooled.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jobType.end-time"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: This element configures terminating time of this job. If terminating time is not given, job will not be terminated.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="loggingGroup.level"><![CDATA[
              [Description]: Level of logging is set for this field. Please refer to Level class of logging API of J2SE.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="file-handlerType.valid-day"><![CDATA[
                      [Description]: File in which this handler uses will be used and updated frequently for certain set amount of time .
                                      This setting is used for changing file as unit of day. In this case, used date will be followed right after file name.
                      [Value Description]: day
                      [Example]: &lt;valid-day>1&lt;/valid-day>
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="jobType.description"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Explaination of this job can be written for this field.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="intervalType.daily"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Time cycle is configured in date unit.
                ]]>          
    </text>
            
    <text key="loggingGroup.name"><![CDATA[
                  [Description]: Specify this logger when you apply the settings for other loggers (jeus.transaction, jeus.jndi, etc.)
		  		 except for basic loggers (jeus, jeus.ejb, jeus.servlet, jeus.jms, etc.). You don't need to specify name in typical situations.
				 If you want to know the logger name, you can refer to the separate logger page.
                                 If logging setting is at <node> or <EngineContainer> and this element is omitted, the name should be jeus logger.
		                 If specified under the engine, it always means the logger settings of each engine. Therefore, the name will be ignored.
		                 For the default container, the name is ignored because the logging settings of the node will be used.
                    ]]>          
    </text>
            
        <text key="oldPoolingType.min"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: The mimimum value of being pooled.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="handlerType.console-handler"><![CDATA[
          [Description]: This handler will be used when logging is left in the screen.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="socket-handlerType.port"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Port of sending messages when generating this handler.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jndi-infoType.export-name"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Actual JNDI name defined in JEUS DD.
            [Example]: &lt;export-name>ACCEJB&lt;/export-name>
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="invoke-httpType.url"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: URI path of RMI Handler Servlet (jeus.rmi.http.ServletHandler) called by HTTP-RMI stub should be configured.
                            This URL configures only Servlet request path except for Protocol, Web Server IP and Port number.
                            Protocol is assumed to contain IP address such HTTP, RMI execution environment and Web Server.
                            ( This means Web Server and Web Container should receive HTTP-RMI request.)
                            Port number should be configured in element(HTTP_port) explained in the following.
            [Value Description]: Servlet Context Path expressing RMI Handler Servlet
            [Example]: &lt;url>/mycontext/RMIHandlerServlet&lt;/url>
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="method-paramsType.method-param"><![CDATA[
                [Description]: Fully qualified class name of parameter of this method is set.
                [Example]: java.lang.String
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="securityPermissionType.description"><![CDATA[
      [Description]: Exaplaination on this security permission setting can be written for this field.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="schedulerType.enabled"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This configures whether to operate Scheduler Service.
            [Defined Value]: [true] : activate it
                             [false]: inactivate it.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="rolePermissionType.actions"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Action for this role permission object is defined. There is no action for role permission
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jsp-engineType.keep-generated"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element determines availabiltiy of storing java source file after generating Servlet Class File through compiling source file generated from JSP page.
                            These files are useful for debugging purpose.
            [Value Description]: This configuration activates or inactivates as Boolean value.
            [Value Type Description]: Boolean
            [Defined Value]: default : true
                                         true : Maintaining Java Source File.
                                         false : Deleting Java Source File.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="socket-handlerType.address"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: IP address of sending messages when generating this handler.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="file-handlerType.append"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: In case where file in which this handler uses already exists, this element will be used for determining
                            whether to be written after the file name. If it has been set as flase, existing file will be deleted.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="res-refType.jndi-info"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element configures export name and reference name of each resource reference to be registered in JNDI of this Engine Container.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="common-handlerType.name"><![CDATA[
          [Description]: The name of handler will be set. At this moment, this name should be set as unique in a logger. This name is used for refering handler including tool.
          [Example]: &lt;name>handler1&lt;/name>
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="keystore-configType.keystore-keypassword"><![CDATA[                        [Description]: Configure the keypassword for keystore file applied to current domain.                    ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jsp-engineType.compile-output-dir"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Through configuring this property,  generated class files can be placed in other directory besides &lt;jsp-work-dir> directory.
                           If this property is not set, class files will be located in jspwork directory. This element is not commonly used.
            [Value Description]: Absolute path used for storing JSP class files.
            [Defined Value]: default : %SERVLET_HOME%\jspwork \enginename\GroupDocBase\DocBase
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="rolePermissionType.excluded"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This disables for users to use role.
            [Example]: &lt;excluded/>
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="smtp-handlerType.send-for-all-messages"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: When messages enter into this handler through using log() method of logger registered in this handler,
                            it determines whether to consider it as the sender object of email. If it has been set
                            as false, messages which are only called through using specific send() method are transmitted.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jobType.class-name"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element is fully qualified name of class to execute job.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="user-handlerType.formatter-property"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Property to parse to formatter when handler is generated.
                            This properties are delivered to formatter through using JeusFormatter.setProperty() method stored in Map object.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="oldPoolingType.period"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Time for object to be pooled is set for this field.
            [Performance Recommendation]:As this value is bigger, time cycle will be enlarged and traffic on server operation will be decreased.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="schedulerType.thread-pool"><![CDATA[
        [Description]: This element configures thread pool used when executing job as multi-thread in schedule.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jobType.begin-time"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element configures starting time of this job. If starting time is not given, job is immediately started.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="loggingGroup.filter-class"><![CDATA[
      [Description]: Fully qualified class name of filter class set in this logger is set for this field.
      [Example]: &lt;filter-class>com.tmax.logging.filter.MyFilter&lt;/filter-class>
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="oldPoolingType.max"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: The maximum value of being pooled.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="methodParamType.method-name"><![CDATA[
                [Description]: Name of method is set.
                [Example]: foo
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="oldPoolingType.step"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Increased quantity will be specified as object to be pooled is increased.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="common-handlerType.level"><![CDATA[
                      [Description]: Specifies the level of the handler. Messages will only be output if the level of the
                      message that passes through logger is included within the specified handler level. (For the Access log, items over the
                      INFO level are not output.)
                    ]]>          
    		</text>
            
        <text key="propertyType.key"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element is the key value of property.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="smtp-propertyGroup.bcc-address"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: The bcc-address of receiver is set for this field.
        ]]>          
        </text>
            
        <text key="jsp-engineType.java-compiler"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element configures Java Compiler for compiling Java source code of eJSP.
                           It is not recommended since default configuration is the most efficent way.
            [Value Description]: Character set and compiler configuring java compiler should be included within system path in order to execute.
            [Defined Value]: [sun.tools.javac] : SUN Microsystems Java Compiler in which "tools.jar" is included is used (This configuration is recommended).
                             [javac] : This element configures external "javac" compiler including in system path.
                             [com.sun.tools.javac] : This is operated in serveral systems. If this operates, this is priotized option since it is more efficent and stable than sun.tools.javac.
        ]]>          
        </text>
                
        <text key="jndi-infoType.ref-name"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: This element can declare reference name to be used in source code.
            [Value Description]: Reference name to be binded in actual JNDI name. This element corresponds with ref-name of J2EE Standard descriptor element.
            [Example]: &lt;ref-name>ejb/AccountEJB&lt;/ref-name>
        ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="user-handlerType.handler-class"><![CDATA[
            [Description]: Fully qualified class name in which user has created is set. This class inherits java.util.logging.Handler and jeus.util.logging.JeusHandler will be constructed.
            [Example]: &lt;handler-class>com.tmax.logging.handler.MyHandler&lt;/handler-class>
        ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="keystore-configType.keystore-password"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configure the password for keystore file applied to current domain.
                    ]]>              
        </text>
               
        <text key="poolingType.max"><![CDATA[
        [Description]: The maximum value of being pooled.
    ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="envType.name"><![CDATA[
        [Description]: Name of environment variable used in code.
        [Example]: &lt;name>minAmount&lt;/name>
    ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="SecurityServiceType.classname"><![CDATA[
        [Description]: Java Class name extending one among jeus.security.spi classes.
        [Value Description]: Java Class Name
        [Example]: &lt;classname>mypackage.MyAutenticationService&lt;/classname>
    ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="smtp-propertyGroup.cc-address"><![CDATA[
        [Description]: The cc-address of receiver is set for this field.
    ]]>              
        </text>
                
        <text key="loggingGroup.use-parent-handlers"><![CDATA[
  [Description]: This determines whether handlers of parent logger will be used for this logger.
    ]]>              
        </text>
        
    <text key="SecurityServicePropertyType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Variable name
                        [Value Description]: Variable name
                        [Example]: <name>filename</name>
                    
                    ]]>             
    </text>           
    
    <text key="loggingLevelType.FATAL"><![CDATA[
			[Description]: This is the level of SEVERE. It supports for compatibility as logger level of JEUS 4.x.
                    ]]>             
    </text>       
    <text key="loggingLevelType.NOTICE"><![CDATA[
			[Description]: This is the level of WARNING. It supports for compatibility as logger level of JEUS 4.x.
                    ]]>             
    </text>       
    <text key="loggingLevelType.INFORMATION"><![CDATA[
			[Description]: This is the level of INFO. It supports for compatibility as logger level of JEUS 4.x.
                    ]]>             
    </text>       
    <text key="loggingLevelType.DEBUG"><![CDATA[
			[Description]: This is the level belonging to FINE. It supports for compatibility as logger level of JEUS 4.x.
                    ]]>             
    </text>       
    <text key="loggingLevelType.fatal"><![CDATA[
			[Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>             
    </text>       
    <text key="loggingLevelType.notice"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.information"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.debug"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.SEVERE"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.WARNING"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.INFO"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.CONFIG"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.FINE"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.FINER"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.FINEST"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.ALL"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Please refer to Level class documentation of J2SE Logging API.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.severe"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.warning"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.info"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.config"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.fine"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.finer"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.finest"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="loggingLevelType.all"><![CDATA[
                        [Enumeration Display]: false
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.oracle"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using Oracle DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.informix"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using Informix DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.db2"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using IBM DB2 DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.mssql"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using Microsoft SQL Server DBMS 
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.sybase"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using Sybase DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.hsql"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using HSQL DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.cloudscape"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using Cloudscape DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="db-vendorType.mysql"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: In case of using MySQL DBMS
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="engineType.EXCLUSIVE_ACCESS"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: Each entity bean instance has exclusive access and a one-to-one relationship with the database row that
  				it represents. This means that the EJB engine can skip all the ejbLoad() calls to this bean since it will know that no 
		    		other entity bean will access and modify the data while the instance is alive. The engine thus calls ejbLoad() only once 
		   		when the bean is created and then assumes that no changes are made to the DB so that no more ejbLoad() calls have 
		    		to be made. This setting can NOT be used when the bean is part of a cluster. It must also be remembered 
		    		that the database should only be allowed to be modified by the WAS (external non-WAS access should be disallowed).
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="engineType.SINGLE_OBJECT"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: With this setting, several EJBs in different EJB engines may be mapped to the same database row. ejbLoad() will 
                     				be called before every request to the entity bean. This setting (or MULTIPLE_OBJECT) is thus required when you cluster EJBs of 
                     				the same type. The difference from the MULITPLE_OBJECT setting is that within each EJB engine, only ONE EJB entity bean will be 
                     				assigned to handle all EJB client requests (thereby the term "single object"). Other requests arriving to the same EJB engine 
                     				while the EJB instance is already tied up will cause the new requests to wait until the processing is finished.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="engineType.MULTIPLE_OBJECT"><![CDATA[
                    [Description]: With this setting, several EJBs in different EJB engines may be mapped to the same database row. ejbLoad() will 
                    				be called before every request to the entity bean. This setting (or SINGLE_OBJECT) is thus required when you cluster EJBs of 
                    				the same type. The difference from the SINGLE_OBJECT setting is that within each EJB engine, serveral EJB entity bean instances 
                    				will be spawned to handle all EJB client requests concurrently (thereby the term "mulitple object"). Other requests arriving 
                    				to the EJB engine while previous requests are being processed will thus NOT have to wait like they do in SINGLE_OBJECT mode.
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="vendorType.oracle"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Oracle JDBC driver
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="vendorType.sybase"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Sybase JDBC driver
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="vendorType.mssql"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: JEUS MS SQL Server driver
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="vendorType.db2"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: DB2 JDBC driver
                    ]]>               
    </text>
                 
    <text key="vendorType.others"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Other JDBC drivers
                    ]]>               
    </text>    
     
    <text key="off-intType"><![CDATA[
               [Value Type Description]: The default value is in non-negative int type. In case where the value is -1, it is considered as off.
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="nonNegativeIntType"><![CDATA[
               [Value Type Description]: This element is int type which is over 0. Thus, it includes values which are over 0 in the range of int type.
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="nonNegativeLongType"><![CDATA[
               [Value Type Description]: This element is long type which is over 0. Thus, it includes values which are over 0 in the range of long type.
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="positiveIntType"><![CDATA[
                [Value Type Description]: The default value is in non-negative int type. It permits values which are over 0 in the range of int type.
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="positiveShortType"><![CDATA[
                [Value Type Description]: This element is used as brokerID of JMS broker. 0  is reserved as local brokerID.
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="off-longType"><![CDATA[
                [Value Type Description]: The default value is in unsigned long type. In case where the value is -1, it is considered as off. 
            ]]>
    </text>
    <text key="fractionType"><![CDATA[
                [Value Type Description]: Rate as float type between 0 and 1.
            ]]>
    </text>           
    <ref key="console-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="file-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-handlerType">smtp-propertyGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-senderType">smtp-propertyGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="socket-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="user-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="system-loggingType">loggingGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="user-logType">system-loggingType</ref>
           
    <ref key="console-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="file-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-handlerType">smtp-propertyGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="smtp-senderType">smtp-propertyGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="socket-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="user-handlerType">common-handlerType</ref>
           
    <ref key="system-loggingType">loggingGroup</ref>
           
    <ref key="user-logType">system-loggingType</ref>
    </description>
