<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<description>        
    <text key="nodeType.default-mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default MIME-Type.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-serviceType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the service routine name to be used in JEUS Web Server.
                        [Value Description]: String within 15 characters.  The value must be unique in ws-serviceType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.user-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user directories for user based service.  
                        	       The JEUS Web Server finds the contents from the configured user directory for the user based web service.
                                       e.g. www.tmaxsoft.com/~user1 : The server will service the contents from the 'user1' user account directory in the operating system.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.service-order"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the precedence of URI and EXT in choosing server and service.
                                       If a Vhost does not have such configuration, it follows the default setting of its node.
                        [Defined Value]: [uri,ext] : URI first and then EXT Section
                                         [ext,uri] : EXT first and then URI Section
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.uri-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: 
                        		This element specific URIs to serve.
                                        If a specific URI is requested, this server will provide the service for the URI.
                                        High priority services can be configured here to have the dedicated servers for high performance.
                                        This value must be one of the names in the URIType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.server-address"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures up to 100 server IP addresses and ports to process client requests.
                                       The load will be distributed with the Round Robin method.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.svr-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server name that processes the URI.
                        	       It is required if WBAPI is used and the value must be one of the WBAPI servers registered in serverType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the connection timeout period of receiving response from the web server.
                        	       If it taks more than this timeout value for a user to receive content, JEUS Web Server disconnects it.
                        [Value Description]: Milisecond
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.server-tokens"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the handling method of the server information in HTTP Response Header Server.
                        [Defined Value]: [Off] : No server information is sent.
                                         [Prod(uctOnly)] : ex. WebtoB
                                         [Min(imal)] : ex. WebtoB/3.1.5
                                         [OS] : ex. WebtoB/3.1.5 (LINUX_i386)
                                         [Full] : ex. WebtoB/3.1.5 (LINUX_i386)
                                         [Custom=xxx/x.x] : ex. xxx/x.x
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-loggingType.format"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the content and record method.
                                       If format is not configured, the default log format is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="expiresType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of Expires.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="accessType.order"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the precedence between allow and deny.
                        [Value Description]: {"deny,allow"|"allow,deny"|"mutual-failure"}
                        [Defined Value]: [deny, allow]: deny is applied first and then allow is applied.  Unmatched client requests are allowed.
                                         [allow, deny]: allow is applied first and then deny is applied.  Unmatched client requests are not allowed.
                                         [mutual-failure]: Clients that are in the allow list and not in the deny list are allowed.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.required-ciphers"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the ciphers to be used for SSL.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="sslType.random-file-per-conn"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies the number of random file to be used to make random seed when establishing the connection via each SSL.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="nodeType.usrlog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user log directory.  The path can be either absolute or relative based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.user"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the operating system user who can operate the web server.
                        	       It is not supported in Windows platforms.  Setting the root account is not recommended.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="error-docType.status"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the HTTP status code
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.method"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the client request method.
                                       The default configuration supports GET, POST, and HEAD and you can disable a method by using ? Option.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.logging"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the logging.  The value must be one of the names of the ws-loggingType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.service-order"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the precedence of URI and EXT in choosing server and service.
                                       If Vhost does not have such configuration, it follows the default setting of node.
                        [Defined Value]: [uri, ext] : URI first and then EXT Section
                                         [ext, uri] : EXT first and then URI Section
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.certificate-key-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the private key file for the certificate.
                                       Generally, the file is stored in the SSL directory of JEUS Web Server.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.port"><![CDATA[                        [Description]: This element configures the HTTP Listener port for JEUS Web Server의 HTTP Listener.                                       It is a required configuration for the web server.                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.method"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the client request method.
                                       The default configuration supports GET, POST, and HEAD and you can disable a method by using ? Option.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the connection timeout period of receiving response from the web server.
                        	       If it taks more than this timeout value for a user to receive content, JEUS Web Server disconnects it.
                        [Value Description]: milisecond
                        [Defined Value]: [0]: disables the timeout feature
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.CA-certificate-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This directive sets the all-in-one file where you can assemble the Certificates of Certification Authorities (CA) whose clients you deal with.
                        	       These are used for Client Authentication. 
                        	       Such a file is simply the concatenation of the various PEM-encoded Certificate files, in order of preference. 
                        	       This can be used alternatively and/or additionally to CA-certificate-path. 
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.icon-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory of icon files that are used for dir index.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.default-icon"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the icon to be used for unknown file types.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.backup"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the failover service for the server group.  
                        	       If a server group is set in this element, it will be backed up in case of a failure.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="domainType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: It sets the domain name.
                    		       The domain name will be encoded along with the host name to be used for license verification process.
                        [Value Description]: String type with no more than 31 characters.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.directory"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the characteristic of particular directory in node.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
 
    <text key="domainType.errordocument"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Followings are 4 types of actions to be taken when an error occurred in Web Server.
	                                            1. Print out the error message defined in source code.
	                                            2. Print out user-defined error message.
                                              3. Forward it to local URL.
                                              4. Forward it to external URL.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.expires"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the information of server response headers.
                                                When transmitting the certain MIME type content, this option specifies the expiry date of the content transmitted in the server response header. 
                                                When client browser connects to the previously visited web site, if the web pages are stored in browser cache,
                                                then browser will download only the updated contents. In this case, the client browser submits a request to Web server for sending back only the expired contents,
                                                while sending the particular MIME type and the expirty date of the MIME.
                                                Web server analyzes the MIME-TYPE and expiry date contained in the client request header, 
                                                and if the expiry date of MIME-TYPE page exceeds the current date, Web server will then send it back to client. 
                                                The expiry date ,which client sent to Web server, is the one that Web sever had sent to client by referring to the configuration file.
                                                The 'expires item' defines the things relevant to the this expiry date setting.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.access"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Used to limit or grant the access authority over the resources in the sever according to client IP.
                                                Access section can apply to DIRECTORY/URI/EXT section, and will limit or allow the access over the resources defined by each section.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.dirindex"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This automatically lists the entire directory structure to client, when client requests particular file such as index.html but such file does not exist.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.server"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Register the services which are to be provided.
                                                Web server processes only the registered services, therefore you must register the service for the newly added server program.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.node"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Set the configuration options of the nodes that compose a Web Server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
             
    <text key="domainType.authent"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the authentication procedure for controlling the client access by user and group.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.alias"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the physical directory path-to-URI 'Alias' in the server.
                                                In other words, the incoming request for the certain URI is routed to the physical directory in basis of the alias rule, then processed by using the resources in physical directory.
                                                User can specify the 'alias' regardless of document root, thereby obtaining greater efficiency in administering the system.
                                                However, the physical directories must be set to absolute path.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.service"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Necessary to specify this option only when directly executing the business logic via Web server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
                 
    <text key="nodeType.webtob-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the absolute path of JEUS Web Server directory.
                                       This path must be same as the value of environmental variable of WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.limit-request-line"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum size (in bytes) of a HTTP Request Line.
                        [Value Description]: bytes
                        [Defined Value]: The default value is 8190 which is the largest allowed value.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.filter-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the filter by which details of HTTP request and HTTP response are to be filtered. 
                        [Hidden]: true
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.expires-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the expiry option in Web Server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.dir-index-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Enter the name of the directory index which is to be specified in the DIRINDEX section.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.error-document-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify a particular page to redirect to based on the HTTP error code.
                                                You can specify the redirect pages for all the HTTP Status Codes except HTTP 401 Status Code.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
            
    <text key="cache-useType.cache-refresh-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the cache refresh time for directory index.
                        [Value Description]: second
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.keep-alive-use"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures keep-alive feature.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.logging"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the logging.  The value must be one of the names of the ws-loggingType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.verify-client"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the client authentication level.
                        [Defined Value]: [0]: Requests no authentication.
                        		 		[1]: The user should show available authentication to the server.
		                        		[2]: The user must show available authentication to the server.
        		                		[3]: The user must show available authentication to the server. However, when the server does not have authentication, the authentication process is not needed.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-aliasType.node-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the node where the alias will be applied.
                        	       So the alias can be another node's directory.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.group"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the operating system group who can operate the web server.
                        	       It is not supported in Windows platforms.  Setting the root account is not recommended.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="vhostType.filter-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the filter by which details of HTTP request and HTTP response are to be filtered.
                        [Hidden]: true
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="vhostType.error-document-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify a particular page to redirect to based on the HTTP error code.
                                                You can specify the redirect pages for all the HTTP Status Codes except HTTP 401 Status Code.     
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="nodeType.group"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the operating system group who can operate the web server.
                        	       It is not supported in Windows platforms.  Setting the root account is not recommended.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.random-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the file to create the seed of the random password generator for SSL.
                        	       If configured, JEUS Web Server creates the seed at booting time to generate the password for SSL.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.listen"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element configures up to 100 IP addresses and ports to listen client requests.
                                           It can be used to listen with a specific IP adress for a machine with multiple IP addresses.
                                           This element cannot be applied together with the 'port' element.
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.svr-cpc"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the number of HTH processes and channels for parallel communication.
                                       If a server process slows down due to processing a large volume of requests, setting up the parallel communication can enhance the performance.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.port"><![CDATA[                        [Description]: This element configures the HTTP Listener port for JEUS Web Server의 HTTP Listener.                                       It is a required configuration for the web server.                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="expiresType.mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the expiry dates for different MIME types of Response.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.port"><![CDATA[
                            [Description]: This element configures up to 100 ports to listen client requests.
                                           Multiple ports can listen simultaneously  but this element cannot be applied together with the 'listen' element.                
                        ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.schedule"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the request handling method for distributing requests to the server processes.
                        [Defined Value]: [RR] : 'Round Robin' distributes a request to an idle server process with Round Robin method.
                                         [FA] : 'First Assign' distributes a request to the server process that has the highest priority among the idle server processes.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.svr-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures what type of the service that the server provides.
                                       The server type can be HTML, CGI, JSV, WEBSTD, TPSTD, SSI, and etc.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.default-charset"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the character set to apply when a HTTP header is missing charcter set setting. 
				       The precedence of the configuration ordered from highest to lowest is Directory, SVRGROUP, VHOST, and Node.
						[Defined Value]: [On] : Uses the standard character set iso-8859-1.
										[Off] : Disables this feature.
										[_charset_] : Uses the specified character set.  e.g. "UTF-8"
		    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="svrgroupType.script-location"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: When specifying the php-related server group, this option specifies the path where php execution modules are actually located.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="sslType.crypto-device"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the SSL external crypto device type.
                        [Defined Value]: [builtin] : standard builtin implementations
                                          [cswift] : CryptoSwift hardware engine support
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-loggingType.option"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the option for logging.
                        [Defined Value]: [Sync]: The server writes the logs on the file without buffering. User logs can be read from the file without any delay. It may reduce the performance due to very frequent I/O task.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.cousin"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element must be configured in multi-node environment.
                                       This element sets the cousin server group to share server processes.
                                       The cousin server group can be either in the same node or the different node.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="expiresType.expires-time"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the expiry date (time).
                                       If the required fields are specified, the expiry date will be set in the Response header.
                        [Value Description]: 1) &lt;code>&lt;seconds>
                                                &lt;code>:  'M': file Modification date + &lt;seconds>
                                                         'A': Access time + &lt;seconds>
                                                &lt;seconds>: Integer value
                                                          Frequently used time samples(seconds):
                                                          1 hour : 3600
                                                          1 day : 86400
                                                          1 week : 604800
                                                          1 month : 2419200
                                             2) &lt;base> [plus] {&lt;num> &lt;type>}*
                                                &lt;base>:  'access' or 'now': access time
                                                            'modification': file modification date
                                                [plus]: optional
                                                &lt;num>: integer value
                                                &lt;type>: 'years', 'months', 'weeks', 'days', 'hours', 'minutes',
                                                              'seconds', 'year', 'month', 'week', 'day', 'hour', 'minute' or
                                                              'second'
                        [Example]: ExpiresTime = "A604800",  ExpiresTime = "M3600"
                                           ExpiresTime = "access plus 1 month", ExpiresTime = "now plus 4 weeks", ExpiresTime = "access 1 month 15 days 2 hours"
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.docroot"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the absolute path of the root directory that contains all served contents.
                                       JEUS Web Server will find the requested content based on this root directory.  The requested URI will be appended on this path to indicate the absolute path of the requested content.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.certificate-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the PEM-encoded certificate file.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.node-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the node where the Server Group sits on.  The node name must be same as one in 'nodename' of node element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.http-out-buf-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the buffer size of a response.
                                       Set this value as 0 to use the caching feature.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-loggingType.valid-days"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:  This element decides whether logs will be stored in a file or daily log will be created as a separate file.
                        [Defined Value]: [1] :  daily log files are created (each file will be created at 12:00 AM
                                         [0 or disable] : logs will be stored in a file.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.user"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the operating system user who can operate the web server.
                        	       It is not supported in Windows platforms.  Setting the root account is not recommended.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="vhostType.expires-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the expiry option in Web Server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="ws-engine"><![CDATA[
                [Description]: This is the top-level XML element for configuring JEUS Web Server
            ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="authentType.type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the authorization control method.  WebtoB currently supports only the basic type.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.ignore"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the files that should not be listed for indexing.
                                       The file names to be ingnored should be listed. Wildcard(*) can be used in the file name.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="domainType.nlive-inq"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the hearbeat check period (in seconds) between multiple web servers.
                                       If the time is set too short, there can be overhead in the network due to frequent heartbeat checks.
                                       If the time is set too long, the status of servers cannot be identified quickly.
                                       This value must be set by considering the network volume and importance of the web service.
                        [Value Description]: second
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of TcpGW
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-aliasType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.listen"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This elements sets the IP address where the service can be provided to.
                                       If the web server has multiple IP addresses, this option can be used to allow services for selected IP addresses.  
                                       One or more IP addresses can be configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="extType.svr-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the sever type to process the previously configured 'mimetype'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.send-buffer-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the TCP buffer size.  For some environment, this configuration can enhance the performance.
                        [Defined Value]: [0] : means the default value of the operating system.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.hth"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the number of HTH (HTTP Request Handler) Process.
                                       HTH is the intermediate process in between a client browser and a service process of JEUS Web Server.
                                       HTH receives and transferes client requests to appropriate service processes.  It receives results from service processes and sends them to clients.        
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.max-user"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of connected users.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.rac-port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the port number used for management process 'wsracd' daemon in multiple web server system.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-serviceType.svc-time"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum service time.
                                       If a service takes more than this configured time, it is stopped and the server sends an error to the client.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.hostname"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the host name field of Http Response Header.
                        [Example]: www.tmaxsoft.com
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="directoryType.default-charset"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the character set to apply when a HTTP header is missing charcter set setting. 
				       The precedence of the configuration ordered from highest to lowest is Directory, SVRGROUP, VHOST, and Node.
						[Defined Value]: [On] : Uses the standard character set iso-8859-1.
										[Off] : Disables this feature.
										[_charset_] : Uses the specified character set.  e.g. "UTF-8"
		    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="directoryType.dir-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the path name by using the path name of the directory to which the configuration settings apply. Path name can be either absolute or relative path based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="directoryType.default-mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default MIMETYPE to be used when a MIMETYPE of a requested resource is not recognizable.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="error-docType.url"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the target URL.  The value should be either a full URL or a path relative to the DOCROOT.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="directoryType.force-mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the MIMETYPE to be applied to all resources in the directory.
                                       If force-mimetype is set to CGI, all resources in this directory will be processed as CGI.  
                                       Therefore all client requests will be serviced by the web server whose server type is CGI.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="expiresType.url"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the expiry date for an URL.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.logging"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the logging.  The value must be one of the names of the ws-loggingType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="keep-alive-useType.keep-alive-max"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of requests you want Apache to entertain per connection.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.env-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the environmental variable file that needs to read by JEUS Web Server.
                        	       If variables are configured in a file and JEUS Web Server needs the variable information at the booting time, the file must be configured in this element.  
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.usrlog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user log directory.  The path can be either absolute or relative based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.admin"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the administrator's profile such as his/her email address.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.admin"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the administrator's profile such as his/her email address.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.syslog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory path for system logs.  The value can be either an absolute path or a relative path based on WEBTOBDIR.
                                       It is only used for redefining the system log directory.  If this element is not configured, the system logs will be stored in Default Path.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="extType.svr-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server name to process the previously configured 'mimetype'. 
                        	       It can be used for assigning a specific server to service a specific mime type.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.vhost-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the URI for a specific vhost.  
                        	       e.g. If all vhosts has the same URI but want to use different SVRTYPE then this element can be configured.
                                       This value must be one of the vhost configured in vhostType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.svr-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures what type of service that the server group provides.
                                       The type can be HTML, CGI, JSV, WEBSTD, TPSTD, SSI, and etc.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.connect-timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the timeout period for Web Server TCP Gateway to connect a target server.
                                       If the target server is not responding within this timeout period, the request is forwarded to another server.
                        [Value Description]: milisecond
                        [Defined Value]: [0] : disables the connect-timeout feature.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.redirect"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the target URI to redirect the request to.  
                                       The server puts the Redirect Status code as the loacation header of the HTTP response when a request is redirected.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.node-port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the port number used for inter-communication of nodes. 
                                       This port number must be configured for multiple JEUS web server system.         
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.limit-request-fields"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of HTTP request header fields.
                        [Value Description]: The number of HTTP request header fields
                        [Defined Value]: [0] : means unlimited.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="extType.charset"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the character set for the 'mimetype'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.env-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the environmental variable file that needs to read by JEUS Web Server.
                        	       If variables are configured in a file and JEUS Web Server needs the variable information at the booting time, the file must be configured in this element.  
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.usrlog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user log directory.  The path can be either absolute or relative based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="authentType.group-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the group authorization information file.
                                       The file lists the groups and the assigned users.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.default-charset"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the character set to apply when a HTTP header is missing charcter set setting. 
				       The precedence of the configuration ordered from highest to lowest is Directory, SVRGROUP, VHOST, and Node.
						[Defined Value]: [On] : Uses the standard character set iso-8859-1.
										[Off] : Disables this feature.
										[_charset_] : Uses the specified character set.  e.g. "UTF-8"
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.error-log"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the error logging.  The value must be one of the names of the ws-loggingType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.tms-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This elements sets the TMS process name to configure TMS for the server group.
                        		TMS, a XA transaction manager, is required when the server group needs access to databases.
                                        TMS process is created using $TMAXDIR/lib/libtms.a and DBNAME in SVRGROUP element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.env-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the environment variable file that is needed when the server group is sharing the environment variables with its assigned servers or interoperating with multiple databases from same vendor in the same node.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.default-mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default MIMETYPE to be used when a MIMETYPE of a requested resource is not recognizable.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-loggingType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.description"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets a description for a specific file.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.limit-request-fieldsize"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum size (in bytes) of a HTTP Request header field.
                        [Value Description]: bytes
                        [Defined Value]: The default value is 8190 which is the largest value allowed.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-serviceType.priority"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the priority of processing.
                                       The value can be set in between 1 and 50, and a higher number gets a higher priority.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.load"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the load balancing service.
                        [Defined Value]: [0]: Dynamic Load Balancing.  If a node cannot handle more user requests, it forwards the requests to other nodes.
                                         [1~255]: Rule based routing.  It distributes the loads to the server groups according to their load portion assigned in this element. Any value from 1 to 255 can be set.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.CA-certificate-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory where you keep the Certificates of Certification Authorities (CAs) whose clients you deal with. 
                        	       These are used to verify the client certificate on Client Authentication.
                                       The certificates should be PEM-encoded.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.keep-alive-use"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures keep-alive feature.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.tail-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the file that contains the header to be placed at the bottom of the indexing.
                                       The file path must be set relative to the indexed directory.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.host-alias"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the host name that can be used as a alias to other host names.
                                       The wildcard (*,?) can be used for this value.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.max-tms"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the minimum number of TMS processes. This element is used when the server group has TMS configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.max-restart"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of times to restart the server process.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.hostname"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the domain name that this virtual host represents.
                        	       e.g. mail.tmaxsoft.com
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="authentType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.listen-backlog"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the size of request queue.  This option is not normally used.  
                        	       It is not a commonly used configuration, however it can be a valuable feature if the web server is receving large number of requests at once.  (FYI, hackers often attacks a web site by sending large number of requests at once)
                                       The requests will be rejected if the size of queue reaches this value.         
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.shmkey"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the value for shared memory segment which is used by JEUS web server processes.
                        		Before this configuration, make sure this key is not used by other programs.  If there is conflict, JEUS Web Server will not boot up.  
                        [Value Description]: The value can be anywhere between 32768 and 262143.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.default-mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default MIME-Type.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.ipc-base-port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the port number for IPC between internal processes.
                                       This option is only supported in Windows.  For previous versions, this port number was set up in the environment variable of 'WEBTOB_WINDOWS_PORT'.
                                       If the port number is set in both places, the value in the environment variable has the precedence.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.max-requests"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of requests that this server can service before rebooting.
                                       If the server processes this number of requests, it gets automatically rebooted.
                                       If an application running on the web server has a bug in memory management, this feature can be used to reset the memory.
                                       If client requests require continuous service, the server may process more than this number before rebooting.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.close-info"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures how to open a database connection.  It uses the command supported by the target database.
                        	       This element is used when the server group has TMS configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="authentType.user-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the file that stores user IDs and passwords.
                                       JEUS Web server provides 'wsmkpw' utility that can be used to set user IDs and passwords.
                                       'wsmkpw' utility stores the user IDs and passwords (encrypted) in the file.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ssl-useType.ssl-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of SSL.  This name must be one of the names registered in 'sslType' element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="ssl-useType.ssl-flag"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: It is a mandatory item that must be specified when using SSL in JEUS Web Server.
                                                If SSLFLAG is set to 'true', and  SSL will be used in the node, if set to false, SSL will not be used.
                                                The default setting is 'false'.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
        
    <text key="nodeType.user-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user directories for user based service.  
                        	       The JEUS Web Server finds the contents from the configured user directory for the user based web service.
                                       e.g. www.tmaxsoft.com/~user1 : The server will service the contents from the 'user1' user account directory in the operating system.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.verify-depth"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the level of verifying other CA's certificates.  
                        	       According to this value, the server tracks the related CAs for verification.
                        	       If one CA should be verified, it can be set up as 1.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.maxq-count"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the size of request queue.  This option is not normally used.  
                        	       However it can be a valuable feature if the web server is receving large number of requests at once.  (FYI, hackers often attacks a web site by sending large number of requests at once)
                                       The requests will be rejected if the size of queue reaches this value.          
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="accessType.deny"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the denied IP addresses and network/netmask.
                        [Value Description]: {"all"|"{ipaddr|ipaddr/netmask},..."}
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.cache-use"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the cache service of web server.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.svc-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the service name of TP service or WBAPI service to use.
                        	       Only required when TP Service or WBAPI service is used.        
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.userlog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the user log directory.  The path can be either absolute or relative based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.certificate-chain-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory path to store Certificate Agent's certificates for Certification Chain setup.
                                       For client authentication, CA-certificate-path or CA-certificate-file must be configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="extType.mimetype"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the MIME type to assign the specific server types.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-aliasType.vhost-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the vhosts where the alias will be applied.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="cache-useType.cache-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the cache entry size that can be used for storing session information.
                        [Value Description]: This value sets the size of an cache entry in Kbytes.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.limit-request-body"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the request body size (in bytes) of a HTTP client request.
                        [Defined Value]: [0] : means unlimited.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.min-tms"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the minimum number of TMS processes. This element is used when the server group has TMS configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.node-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the type of the node.  It can be used to assign a specific role to a server.
                                       e.g. If a node should be used as a proxy server, its node-type can be configured as Proxy.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.svr-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures what type of the service that the server provides.
                                       The server type can be HTML, CGI, JSV, WEBSTD, TPSTD, SSI, and etc.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.option"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the options for indexing.
                        [Defined Value]: [Fancy]: It enables the fancy indexing feature. A column title can be clicked to sort. If clicked again, the sort order is changed. If 'FANCY' is put in this element, it is enabled.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.tcpgw-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of TcpGW
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="filterType.real-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the absolute path for the filter class.
                        [Hidden]: true
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-aliasType.real-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the absolute path for the alias directory.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.ssl-use"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures ssl-name and ssl-flag for the SSL service.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.authent-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the authentication for the server group. 
                                       In order to use authentication on the server group, set the authent name in authent element in this element.  The user ID and password must be configured using wsmkpw utility.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="keep-alive-useType.keep-alive-timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the keep alive timeout period to disconnect the client connections.
                        	       JEUS Web Server will wait for a subsequent request before closing the connection.
                        [Value Description]: milisecond
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="keep-alive-useType.keep-alive"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: HTTP 1.1 specification provides KeepAlive for persistent connections. this can increase download speeds, 
                        reduce the latency of many small HTTP connections, optimize network usage, and even reduce server load.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
             
    <text key="svrgroupType.vhost-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: If the Server Group sits on a virtual host, the virtual host name must be configured here.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="error-docType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of the error document.
                        [Value Description]: String within 31 characters
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="accessType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of access.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.http-in-buf-size"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the buffer size of a request.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.app-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the application directory which is needed when the application is invoked by JEUS Web Server.
                                       It must be set with an absolute or relative path based on WEBTOBDIR for the directory that contains the executable file of the application.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.max-proc"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the maximum number of server processes.
                               	       JEUS Web Server maintains a certain number of server processes and controls the size within the min process # (min-proc) and the max process # (max-proc) for optimal performance.  
                        	       JEUS Web Server can increase the # of server processes up to this value. 
                        	       The performance can be enhanced by assigning the appropriate # of server processes for certain services. 
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.options"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures how to response when a client request URL does not specify a file name.
                                       JEUS Web Server can either display the directory structure or none.  The default configuration does not display the directory structure.         
                                       '+' or '?' Option can be used for this element.  e.g. To display the directory structure, set it up as '+Index'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.txlog-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory path for transaction logs. The value can be either an absolute path or a relative path based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.timeout"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the connection timeout period of receiving response from the web server.
                        	       If it taks more than this timeout value for a user to receive content, JEUS Web Server disconnects it.
                        [Value Description]: Milisecond
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.app-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the application directory which is needed when the application is invoked by JEUS Web Server.
                                       It must be set with an absolute or relative path based on WEBTOBDIR for the directory that contains the executable file of the application.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.svg-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server group that the server belongs to.
                                       This value must be one of the server group name configured in the svrgroup element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.node-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the type of the node.  It can be used to assign a specific role to a server.
                                       e.g. If a node should be used as a proxy server, its node-type can be configured as Proxy.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.nodename"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the Host Name of the server.  If it is set to $(NODENAME), JEUS Web Server will automatically assigns the appropriate host name.
                        [Value Description]: Korean fonts and spaces are allowed.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.app-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the application directory which is needed when the application is invoked by JEUS Web Server.
                                       It must be set with an absolute or relative path based on WEBTOBDIR for the directory that contains the executable file of the application.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the physical node name (host name).
                                       Host name can be found by 'uname -n' command in UNIX.
                                       A logical name can be used and the node name does not need to be listed in 'etc/hosts' file.  However the logical name must be same as the one configured in Nodename element.
                                       One or more node name must be configured.         
                        [Value Description]: String with up to 31 characters
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="filterType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of a filter.
                        [Hidden]: true
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.icon-dir"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the directory of icon files that are used for dir index.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.default-charset"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the character set to apply when a HTTP header is missing charcter set setting. 
				       The precedence of the configuration ordered from highest to lowest is Directory, SVRGROUP, VHOST, and Node.
						[Defined Value]: [On] : Uses the standard character set iso-8859-1.
										[Off] : Disables this feature.
										[_charset_] : Uses the specified character set.  e.g. "UTF-8"
		    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.options"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures how to response when a client request URL does not specify a file name.
                                       JEUS Web Server can either display the directory structure or none.  The default configuration does not display the directory structure.         
                                       '+' or '?' Option can be used for this element.  e.g. To display the directory structure, set it up as '+Index'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-engineType.domain"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This elelment describes the configuration for JEUS Web Server System.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="cache-useType.cache-entry"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element stes the total number of hashing key to be used for caching.
                        	       If a large number of hashing key is used it takes more time to find the hashing key but less time to find the value from the hashing key. 
                                       If a small number of hashing key is used it takes less time to find the hashing key but more time to find the value from the hashing key. 
                                       e.g. Using only A and P vs. using A, B, C...Z as hashing keys
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-aliasType.svr-type"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server type to process a client request for the alias.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="tcpgwType.access-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the users who are allowed to access.
                        	       The value must be one of the names in the accessType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="accessType.allow"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the allowed IP addresses and network/netmask.
                        [Value Description]: {"all"|"{ipaddr|ipaddr/netmask},..."}
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.node-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of the node where the virtual host sits on.  This node name must be registered in Node element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.open-info"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures how to open a database connection.  It uses the command supported by the target database.
                        	       This element is used when the server group has TMS configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.db-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the database name.  
                        	       This element is used when the server group has TMS configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of vhost.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.docroot"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the top level directory with web contents.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.index-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default page to load when a client request does not specify the file name in the URL.  The default page is 'index.html'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.asq-count"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the number of requests on queue as a threshold to activate an additional server process.
                                       If the queue reaches this size, an additional server process will be started as long as the number of the server processes are less than max-proc value.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.index-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the default page to load when a client request does not specify the file name in the URL.  The default page is 'index.html'.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="sslType.pass-phrase-dialog"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the method to get the password phrase for acessing the private key files.
                        [Defined Value]: [builtin] : requests the password phrase when botting the web Server.
                                         [exec:/path/to/program] : executes the program and uses its output as the password phrase when booting the web Server.
                                                                   The program can be either an executable or a shell script.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server name.  The name must be unique within the server element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="ws-loggingType.file-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the file path and name for logging.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.header-file"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the file that contains the header to be placed at the top of the indexing.
                                       The file path must be set relative to the indexed directory.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="cache-useType.cache-refresh-html"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the cache refresh time for HTML.
                        [Value Description]: second
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.ssl-use"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures ssl-name and ssl-flag for the SSL service.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.jsv-port"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the port number used for communcation between JEUS Web Server and Java Servlet Process.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="directoryType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name of the directory.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="svrgroupType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the server group name.  It must be unique within SVRGROUP element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.min-proc"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the minum number of server processes.
                        	       JEUS Web Server maintains a certain number of server processes and controls the size within the min process # (min-proc) and the max process # (max-proc) for optimal performance.  
                        	       JEUS Web Server will initially start this minimul number of server processes at booting time.
                        	       The performance can be enhanced by assigning the appropriate # of server processes for certain services.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="uriType.redirect-status"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the HTTP status when a request is redirected. This value will be set in the location header of HTTP response.
                        [Defined Value]: If not configured, 'found(302)' is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="extType.name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element sets the name for the ssl setting.  String value is used.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="vhostType.listen"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This elements sets the IP address where the service can be provided to.
                                       If the web server has multiple IP addresses, this option can be used to allow services for selected IP addresses.  
                                       One or more IP addresses can be configured.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="nodeType.error-log"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the error logging.  The value must be one of the names of the ws-loggingType element.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="dir-indexType.icon-ext"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element configures the mapping between file extensions and icon image files.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
         
    <text key="serverType.cl-opt"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This elelemt sets the commands for server process initiation.
                                       The options defined before '--' are used by the system and the options defined after '--' are used by users.
                        [Defined Value]: [-e] : -e [file name] It records the standard errors in the file.  A file named [server process name]_[file name] is created to log the standard errors occurred in the server process.
                                         [-o] : -o [file name] It records the standard output in the file.  A file named [server process name]_[file name] is created to log the standard outputs occurred in the server process.
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="sslType.fake-basic-auth"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: If using FakeBasicAuth option, SSL logs users in based on client certificate. it gets the userid from the certificate, 
                                       and then authenticates user by doing a "fake" login using that userid and a password of 'password'.
                                                If specifying this directive with VerifyClient directive, it saves the log of authentication history.                   
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.client-check-interval"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify this option to check whether the clients connecting to WebtoB Server are alive or not.
                                                WebtoB automatically checks the client at the specified intervals, and if the client is dead, the connection will be automatically terminated by Web server.
                        [Value Description]: Milisecond unit
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.svrgroup"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: When accessing to server processes via Web Server, it needs to divide the server processes into groups based on their logical relationship.
                                                This is the item to specify group options.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.logging"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the record type of client request history. The access and error history are individually saved.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.vhost"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Configure the virtual hosting on Web server.
                                                Virtual Host refers to the function of providing each different service via each different URL, and so even though only one server is running, 
                                                but it looks like that multiple servers are running for a service.                                        
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="vhostType.dir-index-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Enter the name of directory index which is to be specified in DIRINDEX section.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.language-priority"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: When connected client does not have specified language, this item specifies the priority of processing multiview request according to the language specified in the server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.tcpgw"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the listener and the server for processing client request. 
                                                the tcpgw listenes on the specified port, and if data comes in, it will send the data to the specified server.
                                                For instance, the tcpgw in the Web server sends the data to the tcp-servlet in JEUS by round-robin manner.
                                                In case of the port limitation due to the firewall, you can use the WebtoB server as proxy server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.filter"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This item enables modifying (filtering) of request or response 
                                       just prior to processing the client HTTP request or sending the HTTP response to the client.
                        [Hidden]: true                                                
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="uriType.uri-def"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Enter URI for the value of service attribute.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="ws-aliasType.uri-def"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Enter URI for the value of service attribute.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="svrgroupType.filter-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the filter by which HTTP request and HTTP response are to be modified(filtered).
                        [Hidden]: true
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="nodeType.ip-permission"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: IPCPERM(inter-process communication permission mask) enables users, not an administrator, to conduct wsdown, start and shutdown of the particular process, 
                                                and even check the result via wsadmin.
                                                In Unix environment, you can give different level of authority  to admin, individual users, groups, etc by setting up the file access control (view/record/execute).
                                                In other words, if set to default, users are not able to use above functions, but if IPCPERM is set to 0777, user can use all the functions.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="svrgroupType.expires-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify expiry options in Web Server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.ext"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]:	This item appoints the process to each client request based on the requested file extension.
                                                Generally the process for each default MIMI-TYPE has already been specified, However in case of additional configuration, you can use this section.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.ssl"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specify the SSL function to be used in Web server.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
     
    <text key="domainType.uri"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This item enables the server to identify the processing service for each URI(Uniform Resource Identifier)value of client request.
                                                In other words, if a particular URI comes in, the specified service will be assigned to process the request with the URI.
                    
                    ]]>        
    </text>
    <text key="directoryType.dir-path"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: This element setsthe directory path using either an absolute or relative path based on WEBTOBDIR.
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>   
    <text key="svrElementType.HTML"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: HTML(HyperText Markup Language)
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>
                                               
    <text key="svrElementType.CGI"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: CGI(Commom Gateway Inteface)
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>
                                               
    <text key="svrElementType.SSI"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: SSI(Server Side Include)
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>
                                               
    <text key="svrElementType.JSV"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: JSV(Java SerVlet)
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>
                                               
    <text key="svrElementType.PHP"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: PHP(Personal HomePage)
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>
                                               
    <text key="svrElementType.WEBSTD"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: WEB API
                    ]]>                                        
    </text>   
    
    
    <text key="directoryType.access-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies whether user access will be allowed according to the settings of access_name within the ACCESS section.
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="uriType.access-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies whether user access will be allowed according to the settings of access_name within the ACCESS section.
                    ]]>     
    </text>

    <text key="extType.access-name"><![CDATA[
                        [Description]: Specifies whether user access will be allowed according to the settings of access_name within the ACCESS section.
                    ]]>     
    </text> 
</description>
